<contract-classes>
  <family source="contents/contract.css">
    h4, paragraph
  </family>
  <family source="layout/container.css">
    containerFluid
  </family>
  <family source="ui/dropdowns/contract.css">
    dropdown, dropdownDivider, dropdownItem, dropdownMenu, dropdownToggle
  </family>
  <family source="ui/navbar/contract.css">
    navbar, navbarBgLight, navbarBrand
  </family>
  <family source="ui/navs/contract.css">
    nav, navItem, navLink, navLinkActive, navPills
  </family>
  <family source="ui/scrollspy/contract.css">
    scrollspyExample
  </family>
  <family source="utilities/contract.css">
    px3
  </family>
</contract-classes>
<component name="ScrollspyExample">
  <jsx>
    <div class="bd-example" class-contracts="theme containerFluid">
      <nav class-contracts="theme navbar navbarBgLight px3">
        <!-- biome-ignore lint: <a> is used for demonstration purposes -->
        <a class-contracts="theme navbarBrand" href="#" onClick="(event) =&gt; event.preventDefault()">
          Navbar
        </a>
        <ul class-contracts="theme nav navPills">
          <li class-contracts="theme navItem">
            <a class-contracts="theme navLink navLinkActive" href="#fat">
              @fat
            </a>
          </li>
          <li class-contracts="theme navItem">
            <a class-contracts="theme navLink" href="#mdo">
              @mdo
            </a>
          </li>
          <li class-contracts="theme navItem dropdown">
            <!-- biome-ignore lint: <a> is used for demonstration purposes -->
            <a class-contracts="theme navLink dropdownToggle" href="#" onClick="(event) =&gt; event.preventDefault()" aria-expanded="false">
              Dropdown
            </a>
            <ul class-contracts="theme dropdownMenu">
              <li>
                <a class-contracts="theme dropdownItem" href="#one">
                  one
                </a>
              </li>
              <li>
                <a class-contracts="theme dropdownItem" href="#two">
                  two
                </a>
              </li>
              <li>
                <hr class-contracts="theme dropdownDivider" />
              </li>
              <li>
                <a class-contracts="theme dropdownItem" href="#three">
                  three
                </a>
              </li>
            </ul>
          </li>
        </ul>
      </nav>
      <div class-contracts="theme scrollspyExample" tabindex="0">
        <h4 class-contracts="theme h4" id="fat">
          @fat
        </h4>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          Placeholder content for the scrollspy example. You got the finest architecture.
          Passport stamps, she's cosmopolitan. Fine, fresh, fierce, we got it on lock.
          Never planned that one day I'd be losing you. She eats your heart out. Your kiss
          is cosmic, every move is magic. I mean the ones, I mean like she's the one.
          Greetings loved ones let's take a journey. Just own the night like the 4th of
          July! But you'd rather get wasted.
        </p>
        <h4 class-contracts="theme h4" id="mdo">
          @mdo
        </h4>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          Placeholder content for the scrollspy example. 'Cause she's the muse and the
          artist. (This is how we do) So you wanna play with magic. So just be sure before
          you give it all to me. I'm walking, I'm walking on air (tonight). Skip the talk,
          heard it all, time to walk the walk.
        </p>
        <h4 class-contracts="theme h4" id="one">
          one
        </h4>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          Placeholder content for the scrollspy example. Takes you miles high, so high,
          'cause she's got that one international smile. There's a stranger in my bed,
          there's a pounding in my head. Oh, no. In another life I would make you stay.
          'Cause I, I'm capable of anything. Suiting up for my crowning battle. Used to
          steal your parents' liquor and climb to the roof. Tone, tan fit and ready, turn
          it up cause its gettin' heavy. Her love is like a drug. I guess that I forgot I
          had a choice.
        </p>
        <h4 class-contracts="theme h4" id="two">
          two
        </h4>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          Placeholder content for the scrollspy example. It's time to bring out the big
          balloons. I'm walking, I'm walking on air (tonight). Yeah, we maxed our credit
          cards and got kicked out of the bar. Yo, shout out to all you kids, buying
          bottle service, with your rent money. I'm ma get your heart racing in my
          skin-tight jeans. If you get the chance you better keep her. Yo, shout out to
          all you kids, buying bottle service, with your rent money.
        </p>
        <h4 class-contracts="theme h4" id="three">
          three
        </h4>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          Placeholder content for the scrollspy example. If you wanna dance, if you want
          it all, you know that I'm the girl that you should call. Walk through the storm
          I would. So let me get you in your birthday suit. The one that got away. Last
          Friday night, yeah I think we broke the law, always say we're gonna stop. 'Cause
          she's a little bit of Yoko, And she's a little bit of 'Oh no'. I want the jaw
          droppin', eye poppin', head turnin', body shockin'. Yeah, we maxed our credit
          cards and got kicked out of the bar.
        </p>
        <p class-contracts="theme paragraph">
          And some more placeholder content, for good measure.
        </p>
      </div>
    </div>
  </jsx>
</component>
